Hello, everyone.
Can you hear me?
Uh, are you all in?
We're about to start.
Okay, well, because now it's because of the epidemic.
So we're all working from home.
So the Internet might not be good.
Everyone is.
And don't be surprised.
Uh, I'm in Shanghai.
I'm in Shanghai, Minhang.
So I'm at home right now.
So a lot of my colleagues are at home.
And so are my roommates.
So the Internet might be a little bit bad.
So if you're all here, then we're going to start.
Okay.
Uh, I'm in Shanghai.
Uh, so what I'm going to talk about next is how to make a suit.
That suit, if you talk about it this time, it has a two-layer material and an outer fabric with a two-layer structure.
And then there's no problem.
I'll just start.
So first of all, we're going to download a version of the suit.
If it's a version, you can just confirm it.
And then we're going to download a virtual model.
If it's a virtual model, you can choose one of your favorite models.
So after you download it, the following is the selected version.
We're going to copy the other side of the version.
Control plus D.
The version with the colon.
Copy it out.
And then after we copy it, we put the corresponding version together.
It's going to be easier for us to sort it out and arrange it later.
After that, the following is to click on the 2D 3D tool bar.
From this 2D arrangement tool.
And then we add two layers of the board.
Just put it all together.
You can see the effect on the screen.
Put it to one.
It's after the selection.
Uh, the locator.
Just move it up.
For the locator, you can right-click in the blank.
It selects one.
Uh, a locator with a world coordinate.
In this case, if you move the angle, its coordinate direction will not change.
And then we look at these small panels.
It's a pocket panel.
And there are these elastic strips.
What about these panels?
We don't do it first.
You can save it.
After saving, you can see the 3D window.
This panel is gone.
So we can.
No need.
We won't be involved in the simulation.
And then we put it down.
Uh, the front and back relationship of the panel.
Put it down.
You can see the sleeve panel inside.
We'll put it down.
Because the ball is blue.
Just move it back.
Put it back.
And then you can make a single adjustment.
And then the other side is the same.
Move to overlap.
And then I push it back.
And then the single panel on the side is also adjusted for them.
And then the other side of the sleeve.
And then just push it back.
And then the back panel.
And then the panel, we try to put it in.
Put it closer.
Then we'll be more stable in the simulation.
And then after that, let's take a look at the front.
Uh, look at this panel.
Oh, he's right.
And then let's take a look.
There's a button here.
There's a button panel.
We have to choose it before we arrange it.
A pre and post arrangement.
A arrangement.
Then here, left plus right or right plus left.
Just arrange it according to your actual situation.
Then on my side, it's on the left to the right.
So I'm going to move this left panel to the front.
And then after that, the next thing is to make a panel arrangement.
We choose this all panels.
This is the front panel.
All of them are selected together.
And then go to the front.
Find a suitable arrangement.
And then after arranging it, we can use this arrangement.
This frame.
Adjust its one.
Uh, the frame is enlarged or reduced.
And then move its position with the positioning ball.
And then the sleeves are the same.
Choose the two layers of sleeves together.
And then find an arrangement.
Uh, back.
Also find one.
And then we're using this positioning ball.
Just move the position.
Uh, the one in the back is the collar.
If the collar is too tight, you can adjust the diameter.
Adjust the diameter.
After all the arrangements are done.
That's what we're going to do next.
2D window.
Do the powdering.
That powdering.
Uh.
A more important point.
Is that you have to sew the knife to the knife.
Because of the suit.
Uh, he.
Uh, for example, like this sleeve.
He's going to have this chain.
There's a chain.
So you have to sew the knife to the knife.
And then I'm going to sew this side seam first.
I'm going to sew the sleeve here quickly.
I'm not going to cut it.
And then the sleeves on both sides.
And then the back.
And then there's the side seam.
It's going to be a little bit more accurate to sew the knife to the knife.
Just as much as possible.
Where there's a knife.
It's going to be a powdering on the knife.
And then this is.
A powdering of the door and the material.
And then the side.
And then the sleeves.
I'm going to quickly sew it here.
So I don't have to.
I'm not going to cut it.
You guys, remember, you can.
How to sew.
And then the material.
On my side, this is where I'm going to finish sewing.
And then the other side is also sewn to this point.
Why don't you sew it to the bottom?
Because there's a fold here.
So later we can.
It's a separate setting of an internal line.
A corner of the line.
So if you sew down to the bottom, the sewing line will also be affected, so I sew it here step by step.
Then fix it on both sides of the back collar.
After sewing, the sewing line type must be changed to a fold seam.
In this case, the simulation will be more even.
Then the other side is also the sewing line type changed to a fold seam.
Then the front door seam is also sewn.
The sewing line type must also be changed to a fold seam.
Then we sew the shoulder first.
Then, if there is a knife opening, try to sew the knife opening.
Then we sew the shoulder.
If the shoulder has a knife opening here, it must be sewn to the knife opening.
You can see that the length on both sides is different.
There is a fold seam on one side.
Then the other side.
Then there is a little seam on the other side.
Then there is a knife opening at the bottom.
Sew from this side to the knife opening.
Then the other side is also sewn from the right side to the knife opening.
Then the back of the sleeve, the knife opening to the knife opening.
Then the bottom is 1-n sewing.
Sew them well.
Then let's take a look at where there is no seam.
Then the bottom is the same.
Then we also sew the next one.
Then it's also here.
Sew a section and then the other two sides.
Press the Shift key to sew to the other section.
Then it's a seam.
Sew this section and the other side.
Then the next one is also tiered.
Then these panels.
We will share it in a week's time.
You can practice later.
And then embroidery, because it's not connected here.
So it can only be tiered separately.
And then there is the side.
Let's use 1BN to sew the free sewing line, 1BN is fine.
Then the next one is to sew the collar, and then this section, and then if we sew here, we will try to sew it to this empty line.
Because this is a fold line.
The reason for sewing here is that we are going to sew it with the front one later.
There is also a fold line here in front.
I can sew it to this line.
In this case, the two lines will be lined up, and then the collar will be more even and aligned.
Then the other side.
Just sew it to this point.
These materials.
It can be shared.
We will share it in the public account in a week.
And then the later processing is that it is made up of materials.
If it is made up, it may have a fold.
And then first of all, we are going to connect this basic line to the inner line.
Then connect it and change it to a 360-degree angle.
It's a angle that folds inwards.
A counter-folding angle.
Then we sew these two sections together.
It's like we're going to change the angle of this seam line.
Change it to a zero degree.
In this case, it's like this line is zero.
Sewing on both sides of zero degrees.
Then the seam line type.
Then it's 360 degrees on both sides.
Sewing.
Then the seam line type is changed to a fold.
Then we change this seam line to a zero degree.
And then here.
After selecting a piece of material.
It only folds inwards on one side.
You can see on the other side.
Because these two pieces are connected.
So we can first remove this piece of material.
Connection.
Right click on the piece of material to remove the connection.
And then we're going to hook it up with a hook tool.
Hook it up to the inner line.
And then there's the collar.
You can see the collar.
I forgot to deal with the connection just now.
Then we can.
Use the adjustment panel tool.
Select the panel.
Then right click.
Help them.
Set it to a left and right symmetrical panel.
Panel and split line.
In this case, it's connected on both sides.
That's what I just did.
So this side is going to be divided again.
And then we're going to hook it up to the inner line.
And then check it out.
See which ones haven't been processed.
You can see that the front fold line is not yet processed.
And then when it's done.
We're going to use this adjustment tool.
Turn this collar over first.
Select this inner line at the 3D window.
You can select it and turn it over.
When it's done.
We can see it on both sides.
There's an intersection before and after.
It's overlapping.
So we can use this positioning ball.
Move it to the front.
WeChat public number.
In the live broadcast room.
In the lower left corner of the live broadcast room.
You can scan the QR code on your phone.
Or you can screenshot it.
Wait a minute.
You can also scan the code.
And then we're going to take the picture.
That's the inner layer.
Also make a adjustment.
See if there's an intersection.
It's connected together.
This one didn't make a choice just now.
And then we're going to move it inside.
Then select the right angle.
And then choose.
Give this right angle to 360.
Then below that's us.
Let's make a turn.
And then the angle is also changed to 360.
And then the back side, it has one.
This one.
It's going to push in.
Then it's also changed to a zero.
Then there is nothing else important, and then the following is to add this button.
That button, we select the button tool in the 3D window, and then click on it in this virtual frame, and you can add a button.
After adding it, we can directly select the button in the frame.
Button, use the selection and move button tool to select the button.
Right-click on the selected button, and then find the button to be copied to the layer.
In this way, it will be copied very quickly.
You can see that there is a button tool.
We select the square button and then point to the button.
You can see that it has been copied.
Then after that, the following is to simulate.
Before we simulate, we have to select all these panels and then print them.
Printing, because it has this fold, that is, it has this angle.
The panel has this fold line, so after we print it, the simulation will be more stable.
Then it can be simulated.
The simulation may not be so perfect.
There must be some problems.
Then let's take a look at this place in front of us.
You can see that this button here is blocked.
There is no simulation stability.
Then we can use this button tool to open this button.
If it is opened, click on the box to select the button.
Click on the box to select the button.
This button will be unlocked.
After that, we can simulate the following.
Then before we simulate, we put this.
Because it has two layers in front of it.
One angle of two layers is 360 degrees.
So both angles are pressed more tightly.
So let's change the angle of the side of this inside to a little smaller.
For example, let's change it to 300 degrees first.
Then put these two sides together.
Then remove the hardening of this side of these two panels.
Let it not be too hard.
Then simulate it to untie it first.
Then we add a fixing pin.
Adjust the simulation.
We pull this fixing pin.
Put a layer in front of it first.
Then put it in.
After that, the fixing pin is removed.
Then we put this button back in place.
Then simulate it.
After the simulation, you can see that there is still this instability.
That may be the inside of this button.
You can also change it to a little smaller.
Select and then change it to 300 degrees.
For example, 300 degrees.
Then here we can move this button out a little bit first.
Then simulate it again.
This will be more stable.
Then you can see a conflict on the right.
It's not hooked now.
You can remove this hook.
This is the state without the hook.
This is equivalent to this button.
Everyone is not involved in the simulation.
So the simulation will be more stable.
You can see that my button moves to the bottom to simulate.
It's still stable.
Then after the simulation is stable.
We can do it again.
You can select it again and simulate it.
And then let's take a look at this next one.
This is the opening.
And then the opening.
I fixed them first in the way of smoothing.
Then do a smoothing.
And this is equivalent to.
It's an angle of a reader.
360 degrees.
Then we do a smoothing on both sides.
After the smoothing is done.
The type of smoothing line must be changed to a fold line.
Then this line is equivalent to the zero line.
We also do a smoothing on both sides.
Then the smoothing line is changed to a fold line.
Then simulate it.
Then take a look.
You can see that there is a place inside.
It's leaking.
That's because just now.
This version of this material.
It's not linked to the back.
So we're going to do a smoothing again.
And then simulate it.
And then after that.
Let's take a look at the inside.
Because it has this fold line inside.
So we can harden it.
And then simulate it again.
And then the bottom is to deal with this side.
So let's select these basic lines first.
The top one.
Select this one above.
And then hook it up to the inside line.
And then we select this one.
A closed pattern.
Right click.
And then hook it up to a board.
Press the shift key.
Select the closed pattern on all four sides.
And then hook up a side.
And then trim the other side.
Press the shift key.
Select all four sides.
And then right click.
Hook up a board.
And then the front one.
There's a base line here in the front.
We select delete.
And then select it again.
And then right click.
Hook it up to a board.
And then the other side.
Because it's linked.
So we can select control plus D.
Just a board linked directly to the colon.
And then the colon comes out.
After the colon comes out, we select these boards first.
We don't divide it first.
Select first.
And then do control plus G.
And then do the reverse activation.
And then the next thing we're going to do is we're going to do this.
This middle line.
Select the middle line.
Hook it up as an inner line.
That hook up.
This is the effect that we're going to turn inside.
You can see it in a moment.
And then when it's hooked up.
We select these.
We select these six lines.
And then we can take a look at the angle.
He's going to be back in a minute.
He's going to turn back.
It's going to fold up.
So this angle is 360 degrees.
He took it to 360 degrees.
Because he's going to turn up in the back.
And then we select these boards.
And then we're going to do a hardening.
If it's hard, it's going to be harder.
So he's going to simulate it himself.
It's going to be better.
You can see the simulation.
He's going to turn it over on his own.
And then here.
You might want to change it.
This place.
And then we're going to use the editing line tool.
Just move the top of this line.
Just move it.
And then I'm going to remodel it.
And then here.
Wait a minute.
Remember to sew them together.
That's it.
And then we're going to take a look at the sleeves.
You can see that the sleeves.
It's not like this.
The bottom is like this.
Turn it up by yourself.
That's probably because of this sleeve.
His space is relatively small.
So we're going to do it manually.
An operation of turning them up.
And then we open the simulation.
Just hide the top first.
And then open the simulation.
And then turn it up.
You can add a fixed needle.
And then turn it over to other places.
That way.
He can do it very well.
Just turn this place over.
And then the other side is the same.
Selected version.
Is it a hidden version?
And then we're going to open the simulation.
Turn it up.
When you're done, you can pause.
After the pause.
And then we're going to press the W key.
Click on the version.
You can add a fixed needle.
And then we're going to do a simulation.
And then turn the other side.
The other side is not turned over.
We also pause the simulation.
You can add a fixed needle.
It may not be very easy to turn.
We pause the simulation.
Add a needle.
Then we change another angle.
And then we turn it over again.
So you can see that.
He can also do it very quickly.
Just turn this.
Turn the fold line over.
And then this.
After all is done.
Then the bottom is to deal with this.
The side.
We'll just go on with this.
And then it's with the extruded version.
And then the side is.
Sign them up first.
I'm going to use the free всп.
Then use free powder here.
Because it doesn't have a dot, it's easier to use free powder.
And the back piece.
After that, we have to select these powder lines.
Because it's overlapping with the top.
So we're going to change it to a fold.
And then we select this board.
Activate first.
Then right click and add it directly to the outside.
In this way, you can see it very quickly.
Help you arrange the right position.
And then we're going to do it again.
This is an analysis of the border and the volume.
First sew this sleeve.
That's good. We can sew it for a while.
Just change this type of sewing line to a fold.
In case you forget later.
If you forget to sew it, it won't be stable later.
It will have a curve.
So you have to sew this type of sewing line.
You can modify it or sew it together.
Select and modify together.
And then sew it.
And then we're going to do the simulation.
Before that, let's take a look at this front piece.
Front piece.
And then this side is on the outer layer.
And then the second layer is the front piece.
There's a material in there.
That's equivalent to what we're going to simulate later.
It's equivalent to the front.
It's going to be in front of you.
The simulation may not be stable later.
So we can use this tool to set it up.
One of its uses is that we select the sheet first.
And then point to another sheet.
It's equivalent to pointing to the first selected sheet.
It's outside the second sheet.
And then the second one is equivalent to the sleeve.
It's outside this side.
Put them under the paper.
And then the side.
And another sleeve.
And then there's the back piece.
And then after everything is done.
Take a look.
You can simulate it.
You can see that it's very stable in the simulation.
It just went inside by itself.
Then do other places.
Do some other styles.
You can also use this method.
Use the method of setting the layer.
In this way, a faster simulation will help you simulate it inside.
Then we'll do the same with the elastic band later.
Using this method, you can quickly simulate the next layer.
And then we put the left and right sides that we haven't sewed on the side.
The seam line on both sides is well divided.
This sleeve has two sides on both sides.
And then the side.
Divide this side all over.
And then check it out.
And then there are these two back pieces.
I'll simulate it.
And then let's take a look at the front.
There's something wrong with the front.
We'll simulate it again.
That should do it.
And then we're going to change the model's action.
And then here we can choose a half.
Open a form of a knowledge.
And then just click to confirm.
Let his arm not be too low.
Just hold this dress.
Just open a half first.
And then the next thing we're going to do is we're going to take a look at this.
Wearing clothes on this model.
Whether there is a light or light or light or light state.
Well, if there is, we can use.
To ask for a full selection of the version of the method.
First of all, select the version.
And then click on the selected version.
He's going to have a locator.
And then you can press a four or six angle.
Let him be on the side.
And then we're going to do a red circle.
To rotate.
For example, for example, he's light.
You can turn it back with the red one.
Let him turn.
And then we're going to simulate it.
And then you can turn it a little bit.
Just don't turn too much at a time.
So if you turn to this arm, it's already.
Leave this dress.
Then the simulation will definitely be unstable.
So just fix it little by little.
Just don't turn too much at a time.
This is looking left and right.
And then we put it in front of us.
And then take a look at this window.
Is this too low or too high?
We can open the simulation and pull it up a little bit.
Just wear it up a little bit.
Just don't be too low.
And then you can adjust it according to your actual style.
And then take a look.
See if there's any other detail.
You have to look at your own style.
And then adjust the effect of his creation.
A little bit higher or a little bit lower.
Look at your style.
And then we.
After adjustment.
We can add some details.
For example, we can add the buttons at the back.
Here.
At the back, I made a fake opening.
So I put the button and the eye in the same place.
So I can add this button and eye first.
Add the button first.
And then select the button and copy it.
Ctrl C, Ctrl V.
Copy the button.
And then put it in the same place.
It's like there are two buttons here.
And then use the select and move button tool.
Right click.
Let it switch to button and eye.
That's it.
And then now we can modify its angle.
Counting window on the right.
It feels about 15 degrees.
It should be about the same.
We can enter a 15 directly.
That's it.
We can quickly do this button and eye.
To do it.
On the other side.
We just have to choose this button and eye.
Select.
After selection.
Then right click.
There is a button and eye.
On the symmetrical panel.
In this way.
You can quickly do this detail on both sides.
And then let's take a look at this collar.
Let's cut a layer.
Because the collar just made a layer.
Now we cut it directly.
It will be faster.
After the collar is done.
We'll simulate it later.
That's it.
Re-simulate.
If you want to put the collar.
It has a sewing line.
That line will be sewn automatically.
So you have to delete it.
After that,
Just simulate it.
Then after that.
We just add the fabric.
For the fabric.
If we don't have time.
If we don't have a fabric.
We can just put it in the pants.
Just choose a harder fabric.
That's it.
And then the fabric of the collar.
We're right here.
The fabric of the collar window.
And then find a collar.
Let's look for it.
There's a color nail.
I think.
Yes.
There are two.
We choose that color nail.
Just drag it over.
And then we just select this plate.
That's it.
We're going to cancel these two.
Because these two.
It's a.
The door.
The door is made of.
A fabric of this suit.
So we're going to cancel it.
And then the rest.
Let's just click on this button.
Down arrow button.
Just drag it over.
And then after the fabric is applied.
Let's improve this quality.
After the improvement.
And then.
It's okay to simulate.
Simulation.
Then the simulation is almost.
You can turn it off.
And then we're going to do this.
Select the right arrow button.
Unlock the backup.
Because we're going to use it now.
So let's unblock it first.
Unlock it.
After that.
The next step is to smear it.
If you smear it.
One thing to note is that.
There's a knife on top of it.
Smear it on one side.
And then the next thing.
It's going to smear it.
There's a blue dot.
But we don't smear it to the blue dot.
We're going to sew it down a little bit.
It's like.
Sewing one more.
One to two centimeters or so.
Make it have a.
An effect of pulling up.
A little more.
And then.
Then.
And then the other side is the same.
We're going to sew the elastic band on top first.
And then we're going to sew it down.
This sleeve.
And then we're going to sew it down a little bit more.
One to two centimeters or so.
And then we sew it up.
We just choose.
And then right click.
Just add it to the outside.
After adding it to the outside.
I'll simulate it.
It's still out there.
So we can set it up.
Set it up as a tool.
Let them specify.
It's this.
The sleeve is on the outside of the elastic band.
So choose the sleeve version first.
And then under the paper.
The elastic band is fine.
And then the other side is the same.
Choose the sleeve.
And then under the paper.
Let it be outside the elastic band.
And then you can open the simulation below.
You can see that the simulation will slowly go inside by itself.
And then we choose.
And a sewing line of the sleeve.
After choosing.
We can change this sewing line.
A 220 degree angle.
Let him go inside.
An effect.
Later.
You can simulate it.
An effect.
You can see.
He's going to have a bit of this now.
The effect of the sleeve sticking out.
Then.
Then we can also add a little bit of this embroidery.
This is a straight line.
Just don't let it change shape, just add a little bit of a straight line.
Then we can make this a little bit bigger.
After the conflict is enlarged, the safety distance between the two panels will be greater.
So the effect of the molding will be a little better.
Then let's take a look at the other one.
We can also add a little bit of this layer.
Right-click on the layer and you can add a layer.
Then slightly simulate.
Once the simulation is done, you can pause it first.
Take a look at its effect.
Here we can choose this flange line again.
Change its angle to a angle of 220 degrees.
It also has a little bit of the effect of digging into it.
That's up to your own needs.
If you want to dig deeper, you can make the angle a little bigger.
Just make it a little bigger.
This is just a method.
You can use this method to adjust it.
Then take a look at it again.
Then we add this switch below.
There are two in the elevator.
One is 4mm and the other is 8.5mm.
We choose the thin one.
Then here we choose to increase.
Then confirm.
Is it necessary to load this position and the size of the virtual model here?
We choose no.
If you choose yes, this model dress will be separated from the model.
Then we choose no.
Then turn this dress back on.
Hide it.
Then we choose this switch.
Then adjust it first.
Then we can put the switch.
A layer or pressure.
Change the pressure to a negative one first.
One of the functions of changing the negative is to simulate later.
It will be more attached to the model's body.
Then we change its layer to a negative one.
One of the functions of changing it to a negative one is that we will activate this dress later.
If you need to simulate.
Without this negative one, the elevator will fight with the clothes.
It will not be stable.
So we change a negative layer first.
Then simulate.
You can see that it will be more attached to the model's body.
Then the next step is to adjust this switch alone.
Take a look.
Where to put it is more suitable.
Then we can adjust it again.
Then there is no problem.
Then we can choose to freeze this switch.
Because after the switch is processed.
Generally speaking, you don't have to participate in the simulation.
It's not that you don't participate in the simulation.
You don't need to simulate the shape.
So we can freeze it.
The freeze still exists.
It's still in the simulation.
So we freeze it.
Then you can see this switch.
Now it's outside the clothes.
So we can select the switch first.
Then move down.
Move to the virtual model.
Go inside the clothes.
Then activate this clothes.
Then we can simulate.
Because this switch.
It has already set a negative layer.
So if you simulate it.
Other versions will be faster.
Run outside.
There will be no conflict with it.
You can choose the version in the 3D window.
Then right-click.
There is a version of the anti-evaporation.
Just click it.
Then we look at this.
Now this switch is below the skin.
Now we can move up a little bit.
Then simulate.
Slowly move it up.
In this way, it will be more stable.
Then we can move up a little bit.
Then simulate.
Slowly move it up.
Then it will be more stable.
Then we can move up a little bit.
Handy.
For the beginner's lesson.
You can see another video on the Bilibili.
Then we move it up a little bit.
Put this position.
adjust.
OK.
And now I'm going to make it a semi-transparent display, and what we're adjusting now is that the average of this switch and this
A distance of about a centimeter will be different from this dragon.
You can see this black one and this yellow one.
This line on the outside is about a centimeter away.
In fact, it should be about a centimeter away.
So we can choose and move it a little bit outside.
In this case, it will look better when it is simulated.
Then adjust it, and then we just simulate it.
This is some details, so you may have to adjust it for a long time.
So you may have to adjust it for a long time.
If you are familiar with it, the details will be more fast.
So you have to practice more.
And then some of the ways to do this.
You can just practice it slowly.
And then we'll get rid of it.
And then we'll do some other details.
So after we've adjusted these, we can freeze all the panels.
So we have two more of this behind us.
The pocket is probably not done.
So we select it first.
Then right-click to remove the storage.
Then we hook this basic line to the inside line.
We're going to do a test later.
So we're going to hook it up to the inside line.
And then after we hook it up, we're going to do some
Then you can sew the top or the bottom
These two lines
I sewed this one on the top and this one is broken
And then about
Fix the bottom part as well
And then after sewing, we don't need to move the panel to the place where it needs to be simulated. We just select the right arrow
Just add it to the outside
It's going to be a little bit faster and easier
That's added to the outside or the side is based on the sewing line if you have two panels on the side and on the side so it's added to the side
So it's sewn to the front of it
You just add it
Add it to the front and sew it to the back of it and add it to the back
And then there's a little detail on the lid
I don't know what the name is
You can you can take a look at one of the effects that he can come up with
It's a little strip of paper that you flip over
Okay, sewing line type
Modification
And then it's the same
We select and then right-click to add to the outside
And then there's the addition to the outside
These details are not too much sewing line
For example, you have another panel and another panel and another panel and three panels
If you sew them all together and then add them, there may be a deformation of the panel and so on
So if you add it, try to have a little less sewing line
Just try not to have too much
Just between the two panels
Just add it slowly
Don't sew a lot of panels at once
And then add them one by one
In this case, there will be
The panel is a pull effect
So between the two panels
So less sewing line
Add it again
It's going to be more stable and faster
And then we're going to go down there
After sewing, then simulate it
And then we add some layers to these small panels
For example, the edges
And then the door and the collar
Put these options
After the selection of this selection
Then we add layers
Not side layers
It's the side layers
There's one side layer on the right side
Then there will be a side layer inside
Just click on it
Then add it
Let's simulate it a little bit
Give me the cover first
I'll have some time
Then let's take a look at the details.
We can add it a little bit thicker.
Increase the thickness on the right.
Add to 2, 2 is a little thick, we are a little smaller, about 1.5.
Don't be too thick.
If you have a double layer, you can also select it.
Just open the double layer.
And then the collar has two layers here.
We can add thickness.
And then we come to this button.
Now it's white.
We can change a color.
Change a black.
And then there's a button.
One of its materials, we can change it to a plastic one.
And then the color of the eye.
And then we can take a look at one of the effects inside.
This one inside it.
If you want to change the color of the version, you can also choose one of the materials inside.
And then change the color and so on.
Just modify it.
And then some other details and so on can be adjusted in this state.
For example, like a button and so on.
You can move it and put it in its place.
All right.
Then this state, his arm is half a.
Then you can change a move.
Put his arm all the way down.
An A-shaped effect.
That's what we call an A-shaped one.
It's a state where you put your arms down.
After you put it all down, you can see it.
The effect of this protrusion on the shoulder will be a little better.
And then the next one is this suit.
Then you're in the process of doing it.
There must be some other problems.
Maybe you still have to adjust it.
It's impossible to do it in one step.
You may have to modify it and so on.
Adjusting that adjustment.
After that, this suit is done.
That's what you're going to do next.
We're going to make this suit an open effect.
No matter if it's a good dress or some other effect.
We can do an open effect with the backpack and so on.
That open effect will do it.
It's also relatively simple.
It's not too hard.
The first step is that we're like a real machine.
We don't simulate the rest.
We choose.
Do a freeze.
In this way, other places will not transform.
Then this line will stay there.
All I have to do is open this left side.
I'll freeze it if other places don't move.
That's the next thing.
Unlock this button.
Select the frame.
And then the frame button.
You can take them.
Unlock a relationship between the buttons.
That's the same as the actual one.
There's no button on it.
Then we can open the simulation.
And then move it.
This is an effect of opening the board.
Then we can print this side first.
Printing is going to be a little harder.
Wait a minute.
It's not easy to transform.
And so on.
Then open the simulation.
After opening the simulation.
Then we.
Just use this little hand.
Hold down the main button.
Then drag it.
That's it.
In this way, it will have an open effect.
That's the process.
Just don't be too hard.
You might have to pull this dress a little bit.
Because it's 3D after all.
It's not the same as the actual one.
So you don't have to pull it too hard.
That's it.
Then.
For example, like other backpacks.
The effect of opening.
It's the same.
Backpacks are usually zipper.
We can untie the zipper.
Then the simulation.
Then slowly pull it apart.
Then it will have an open effect.
Then.
Then is.
In the process of opening it up in the simulation.
You can borrow some tools.
For example, the pin.
We can add the pin.
And then open the simulation.
Move this pin.
In this way, it will be fixed in place.
where it will be fixed, and it will not be easy for it to run back by itself after opening the model.
This will speed up the opening a little bit.
The fixed needle is to press the W key and then click on the board to add a fixed needle.
In this way, the effect of our opening is basically done, and if you want to open it on the other side, it is the same.
After opening this side, we can freeze it first, and then untie the other side, and then open the other side.
Now that we've opened the simulation, because it's hard inside, so it's going to be a little bit harder, so now we're going to open the simulation and we're going to pull it a little bit, pull it a little bit, so that the inside of this
material is not too hard, so that it has this soft effect.
Just pull it a little bit like this and pull it a little bit.
Just pull it a little bit so that it's not too hard, it's too flat, and it's a little bit of this kind of wrinkle effect.
And then after opening it, for example, it has this pocket inside, which is the insert belt, and then you can sew this insert belt on it when you open it.
You can put it on.
Open it first.
Freeze it, and then put the effect of this insert belt on it first, add it to the inside or the outside, add it to the outside, and then simulate it, and then the effect inside can be made.
So, when you work on something untilAt 9 o'clock and you are in the studio, you can see that the earring isn't a little bit worn on which person.
So, it's kind of like that.
Now, I'd love it if you could demonstrate that it's soft and it's comfortable on which person, but even if it's not personal, I think you should be able to pretty much do it perfectly and basically look finished.
So, let's see what the changes look like.
Time to do it then.
And here we go.
And that's it.
So now we're going to take out the classic slide.
And this is my Bigby guy.